# Alex Li

#### Profile:

Full stack developer/architect/Team Leader.

I have 15+ years development experience with web/app/backend/solutions.

From small project to large one, I attended as developer, architect and PM etc and carry out too many project successfully.

Last a few years, i built and leaded several projects such as ERP, MES, Travel booking and delivery system etc.

Also I had developed several mobile apps and web apps too.

I'm looking forward to long-term remote development task.

### **Skills Summary:**

Main focused area

- Travel Booking Service Development
- Delivery Service Development
- ERP/MES/CRM
- Blockchain Solution Development
- Other Web/Mobile Apps

#### **Technical Stacks**

- backend : golang/nodejs/asp.net/laravel/j2ee spring
- front : reactjs/angular/vuejs/jsp/php/wordpress
- app : iOS/android native, react-native

#### Others

- ibm cloud/AWS/Google cloud
- mysql/postgres/db2/mssql/oracle/mongodb
- docker/kubernates/Jenkins
- Selenium/Junit/Jest
- firebase/kinvey

#### **Qualifications:**

Master's Degree of Computer Science

### Languages:

Chinese, English

## **Education:**

- 2001 2006 Beijing Information Science & Technology University, Computer Science
- 2006 2008 Beijing Information Science & Technology University, Computer Science (Master's Degree)
- 2009 OOP Developer Course(LGCNS)
- 2012 OOP PM Course(LGCNS)
- 2014 CCNA Training Course(CISCO)

#### **Employment History:**

### Nova China, China

S/W Architect/Engineer

2012 - 2015

- DLP Solution Development(Windows Kernel Driver/C++)
- IPTV Service Platform Development(Java/J2EE, iOS/Android)
- Cambodia Network Center S/W Group Development(NMS, TMS, DMS, SMS)
- ETL Solution Development(Java/SWT)

## **Neusis, USA(Remote)**

Web/Mobile Developer

2016-2017

- Tommy Now, Tommy Snipsnap, Roar for us, Milkcrate App development(React Native, Unity)
- Video CMS Development(AngularJS/Php)
- Cloud File Sharing Solution Development(Electron)

#### Room-Res, Australia(Remote)

S/W Architect/Engineer

2018-2019

Hotel Booking Service Development(React JS, PHP, golang)

## ShengTianYang, China

S/W Team Leader/Architect

2017-

- Transport Delivery System(Angular, Nodejs)
- Skycoin Backend/Admin Panel Development(golang, angularJS)
- MES System development(golang, reactJS)
- ERP System development(ASP.NET, ReactJS)
- Blockchain based web/solution development such as coin development, mining, exchange platform, presell service, gaming and other services